// jshint esversion :6 
// Questions array which is exported to script.js //
export const quizQuestions = [{
        question: "What city did house music come from?",
        options: [
            "San Francisco",
            "New York",
            "Miami",
            "Los Angeles",
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What category of music does house fall under?",
        options: [
            "Dance",
            "Hip Hop",
            "Rock",
            "Country",
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Who was the man behind the name Mr. Fingers and tracks such as 'Can You Feel It'?",
        options: [
            "Larry Heard",
            "Larry Star",
            "Larry Heath",
            "Larry Levan",
        ],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "This man is behind classics such as 'Move Your Body', 'I Got Da Feeling' and 'Mushrooms'. What's his name?",
        options: [
            "Seth Troxler",
            "Jeff Mills",
            "Robert Hood",
            "Marshall Jefferson",
        ],
        correct: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What company designed the legendary tr808 and tr909 drum machines?",
        options: [
            "Moog",
            "Ableton",
            "Roland",
            "Samsung",
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who founded the record label Trick?",
        options: [
            "Patrick Topping",
            "Jamie Jones",
            "Krystal Klear",
            "Afrojack",
        ],
        correct: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What country is Tomorrowland festival held in?",
        options: [
            "Brazil",
            "Belgium",
            "England",
            "U.S.A",
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What BPM range is most house music produced in?",
        options: [
            "50-80",
            "80-110",
            "110-140",
            "140-170",
        ],
        correct: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Who produced 90s dance classic Insomnia?",
        options: [
            "BICEP",
            "Faithless",
            "Depeche Mode",
            "New Order",
        ],
        correct: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the youngest D.J to headline Ultra Music Festival?",
        options: [
            "Armand Van Helden",
            "Tiesto",
            "Avicii",
            "Martin Garrix",
        ],
        correct: 3
    },
];